Robert Reynolds

1331 N Fairfax Blvd, Ranson WV 25438

Phone: (304) 841-1786, Email: robert@robertreynolds.net

Summary

Experienced business and technical solutioning professional with proven accomplishments in planning and leading customer focused solutions. Skillful communication with executives, vendors, customers and internal departments, and motivating directly supervised teams. Excel at cloud-based solutions with AWS.

Experience

Founding Member at Reycom LLC

May 2017 - present

Bootstrapping cloud-based solution for insurance carriers to automate new client loading from diverse producer (broker) inputs.

Senior Solutions Architect at Benefitfocus

July 2010 - April 2017

Provide technical solutioning, commercial service definition, sales value points and client ROI, contract template and early adopter sales support for life & ancillary insurance product carrier program, as well as several small insurance carrier client specific solutions. Sales engineering support of standard products.

Director of Sales at MIND CTI

May 2001 - May 2010

Pre-sales support and delivery of 107% of US revenue goal in 2009 for over \$7.7 million. Defined and led delivery of key new solution modules including Point-of-Sale, Inventory and Revenue Assurance systems. Developed and maintained strategic partnerships, joint solutions and lead generation with industry leaders such as Cisco, Oracle and Sonus.

Director of Site Service at Open Port Technology

November 1995 - October 2000

Developed the deployment program for both direct delivery and partner delivery, managed the deployments for major accounts such as Motorola and UUNet. I developed internal operating procedures and tools from startup with cross-functional teams from engineering, product marketing, sales, and department leads.

Project Manager, Senior System Analyst at SHL Systemhouse

January 1994 - November 1995

Assisted Sales in the development and presentations of RFP responses for the successful \$150 million acquisition of National Steel's IT Department.

Robert Reynolds Page 1

Analyzed, designed and developed key modules in a Planned Benefits management system for Mercer using OO Design methodologies such as Booch. I lead a team of seven engineers in implementation.

Prior Experience in Software Development

Systems Engineer at Wizdom Systems Incorporated

July 1992 - December 1993

Programmer Analyst at Medicus Systems

March 1991 - July 1992

Computer Programmer at Systems Compatibility

January 1989 - February 1991

Computer Programmer at Micro Managers

January 1988 - November 1988

Computer Programmer - Staff Position at Harlow Primate Lab, University of Wisconsin

August 1986 - January 1988

Education

MBA - Finance, Project Management

Keller Graduate School of Management August 1997

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science

Loras College December 1985

Certifications

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Professional

Amazon Web Services December 2017 – December 2020

AWS Certified DevOps Engineer - Professional

Amazon Web Services November 2017 – November 2020

AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

Amazon Web Services September 2017 – September 2020

AWS Certified Developer - Associate

Amazon Web Services October 2017 – October 2020

AWS Certified SysOps Administrator - Associate

Amazon Web Services October 2017 – October 2020

Certified Employee Benefit Specialist (CEBS)

International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans (IFEBP) September 2016

Retirement Plans Associate (RPA)

International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans (IFEBP) September 2016

Robert Reynolds Page 2